This concludes our
practical guide to
financial instruments for trading
and investing specialization.
With these courses, we
intended to explore
how capital flows
around the world,
and how these markets are linked
by various asset classes.
Our journey covered
fundamentals of equities,
which looked under the
hooded corporate accounts.
We also examined how
the business cycle
affects companies and
how investors might navigate
changes in the economic cycle.
Next, we looked at
trading around the world,
introducing you to
foreign exchange,
explored why the currency
market exists and
what considerations there
are when trading in
a currency other than your own.
We then traveled on to
fixed income assets such
as corporate and municipal bonds.
We navigated what those
markets were about,
who issues bonds and why as
well as interest rate moves and
what impact those rates have
on various bond markets.
Next, you were introduced to
the options and futures markets
to better understand
their function,
why they're needed, and
popular strategies to help
you participate in those markets.
You should now have
a solid grounding
in global trading
and capital flows.
During the courses, we use
the IV Keras Traders'
workstation trading platform
and offered some
practical demonstrations.
But you haven't done so already,
you may want to open a
simulated trading account
at no cost and
without obligation.
You'll find the
link to sign up for
the simulated account throughout
the reading materials.
Should you apply for a
paper trading account,
you'll also have access to
any of the news, research,
delayed market data, and
free tools available
to all clients.
Plus you can continue to
explore other
financial assets and
fine tune your
understanding of the ones
we've covered in these courses.
We thank you for joining us
and welcome your feedback.
I'm [inaudible]
Interactive Brokers,
wishing you good luck on
your investing journey.